<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iconic sections</title>
    <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on iconic sections</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to purse some Azure certifications to improve my understanding of the product and bolster my resume. I generally like to start these types of efforts at the beginning, which means revisiting the fundamentals to ensure I have a good foundation. So, for this particular journey that means starting with an Azure Fundamentals certification by taking the AZ-900 exam.
To keep it interesting, I though I might takes notes on the process here as I work through the free training Microsoft provides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/resume/</guid>
      <description>Timothy Adams
Job Type: Permanent
Work Schedule: Full-Time
Desired locations: United States – FL or Remote
WORK EXPERIENCE Solutions Architect, Innovation and Research
University of South Florida, Health Informatics Institute – Tampa, FL
January 2018 to Present - Hours per week: 40
The mission of the Health Informatics Institute is to support the study, prevention, and treatment of diseases in a comprehensive and interdisciplinary fashion by establishing expertise in biomedical science, software and data engineering, and integrative bioinformatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Versioning in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/api-ver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/api-ver/</guid>
      <description>Versioning is an important aspect of API design and implementation. We want to be able change our service and add new features while still providing a stable API that our users can consume. To that end I recently spent a little time with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s aspnet-api-versioning library to learn how it provides an easy way to add different verioning semantics to your API project.
These libraries are really easy to get started with and there are a handful of useful samples here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build your static site with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 20:38:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In a pair of previous posts I described how to host a static site in Azure storage and also how to use a CDN to map a custom domain to your site with https. For each of those examples I used a simple &amp;lsquo;hello world&amp;rsquo; html page, but in the real world we are going to want more out of our site. In my research I came across Hugo and decided to give it a go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use a custom domain with your Azure static site</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-cdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 22:29:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-cdn/</guid>
      <description>In a previous post we looked at how to host your static site in azure blog storage. We stopped with a simple &amp;lsquo;hello world&amp;rsquo; page.
Unfortunately the default address for you site will be in the somewhat undesireable format ..web.core.windows.net. For this blog that is: https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/. Obviously, we might to use a domain we already own. Fortunately, there are some options for this.
We will use an Azure CDN to configure our custom domain endpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to host your website on Azure</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 11:53:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/posts/azure-site/</guid>
      <description>One useful feature of Microsoft Azure that has recently achieved general availability is the ability to host static websites in Azure storage. This blog is an example of such a site, so I thought I might put together a series of posts describing how I built and hosted it. This first installment will cover setting up a simple site in Azure.
I will assume that you already have a Microsoft Azure subscription, but if not you can get started with a free account here: Microsoft Azure Free Account</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timblog.z19.web.core.windows.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi. Some call me Tim.
A little about me:
I am a technologist with a love of learning, and like to think of myself as a producer of complex, creative knowledge work. As a technical leader and architect, I am currently working on software to make academic clinical trials more accessible and effective. Over the 20 years that I have worked with technology in higher education, academic research, and clinical trials, I have come to realize that I enjoy building teams as much as building products and developing strategy as much as I enjoy developing applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>